<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/black_gradient"
    android:layout_gravity="top|center"
    android:foregroundGravity="top|center"
    tools:context=".AboutActivity">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:layout_gravity="top|center"
        android:foregroundGravity="top|center"
        android:padding="10dp"
        android:gravity="top|center">

    <TextView
        android:padding="5dp"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:textSize="18sp"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:text="This app is based on the process of programming an application, however, you do not have to know anything about programming to play this game.\nHere's how the game works: Your character is the white graphic at the bottom of the screen looks like the below image."
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        tools:ignore="HardcodedText" />

    <Space
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="5dp"/>

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/player2"
        android:layout_width="50dp"
        android:layout_height="31dp"
        android:adjustViewBounds="false"
        android:cropToPadding="false"
        android:padding="10dp"
        android:scaleType="center"
        android:scaleX="1.25"
        android:scaleY="1.25"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/ic_baseline_android_24"
        android:contentDescription="@string/android_logo_player_icon_description" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:padding="5dp"
            android:text="After you select your gamemode and difficulty, to play, drag this character around the board and collect &quot;optimizers,&quot; which are the purple puzzle pieces. At any time, there are 6 optimizers around the board, with a new one generating each time one is collected. Your score will be shown in the top left corner, where it will say &quot;Optimizers: 0/25&quot; The left number, 0, is your current score, and the right number, 25, is your goal. This goal is determined by your chosen difficulty level. Once you have reached this goal, a new tile will appear, cycling through the colors of the rainbow. Move your character to this rainbow tile to win the game. There is more to the game than just this however, you must be careful not to have too many &quot;issues&quot; or you will loose. Your Issues will be shown in the top right corner, where it will say &quot;Issues: 0/10&quot; The left number, 0, is your issues count, and the right number, 10, is your max issues count. The max issues count is determined by your chosen difficulty level. Upon reaching this limit, you will loose. Your issues count is basically your HP, but you want the number as low as possible since, if you reach this limit, it's game over. How do you get issues? When colliding with orange, red, or magenta tiles, you may gain issues. Lets go over every tile type one by one. Green tiles are called &quot;safe'' tiles. They are the main path for you to navigate the board on, and they do nothing. Cyan/teal tiles are &quot;fix&quot; tiles. Upon touching them, they will remove 1 issue from your issue count, but will disappear with a chance of generating a new one. Tiles with purple puzzle piece icons are &quot;optimizer&quot; tiles. There are 6 of these tiles, and they always disappear and generate a new one when you collect one. As mentioned previously, these are how you gain score. Orange/yellow tiles are &quot;warning&quot; tiles. These give you one &quot;issue.&quot; These are the less severe tiles, and it is generally safe to use them as shortcuts, as long as you keep an eye on your issue count. Red tiles are &quot;error&quot; tiles. These add 2-3 issues, and make a few random tiles one stage worse, so orange turns to red, red either turns to black or white, black sometimes turns to magenta, and magenta sometimes turns back into black(more on black and magenta later). White tiles are &quot;tile bomb&quot; tiles. When hit, they explode, causing several random tiles on the map to change to random tile types. They do not add issues, but they make it much harder to navigate the map. Black tiles are &quot;crash&quot; tiles. These are an instant game over. Be careful around them, it is easy to accidentally clip a corner and loose from this tile. Magenta tiles are &quot;glitch&quot; tiles. These can only appear after hitting an error tile, or another glitch tile. If you hit this tile, you have a chance of gaining issues, and the glitch tiles may spread, creating new glitch tiles to appear around the board, like an infestation.\n\n\nThis app is still a work in progress, there may be bugs or unimplemented features right now, be mindful of that.\n\nProgress is slow and unscheduled, as it is only a project being worked on for fun by a single developer. Months might go by with no progress, there could be a lot of progress in a brief period of time, or the project could be forgotten and abandoned. There is no schedule or commitment to this app, but there is no plan to stop development anytime soon.\n"
            android:textColor="@color/white"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            tools:ignore="HardcodedText" />


    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>